"annotation_id","annotator","created_at","id","label","lead_time","text","updated_at"
3,"1","2025-02-23T11:44:54.849850Z",1,"[{""start"":82,""end"":90,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":98,""end"":109,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":113,""end"":120,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":124,""end"":135,""text"":""February 19"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":151,""end"":155,""text"":""1998"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":211,""end"":215,""text"":""2017"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":217,""end"":226,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":231,""end"":236,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":259,""end"":266,""text"":""England"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":42,""end"":52,""text"":""eight-year"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":246,""end"":251,""text"":""twice"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":4,""end"":7,""text"":""ICC"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":8,""end"":24,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]}]",116.105,"The ICC Champions Trophy returns after an eight-year gap, with defending champion Pakistan facing New Zealand in Karachi on February 19. Introduced in 1998 to support non-Test nations, it was discontinued after 2017. Australia and India have won twice, while England remains the only major team without a title.","2025-02-23T11:46:28.312868Z"
4,"1","2025-02-23T11:47:40.611716Z",2,"[{""start"":39,""end"":50,""text"":""eight years"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":4,""end"":7,""text"":""ICC"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":8,""end"":24,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":76,""end"":84,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":92,""end"":103,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":107,""end"":114,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":118,""end"":129,""text"":""February 19"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":153,""end"":157,""text"":""1998"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":217,""end"":219,""text"":""12"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":233,""end"":237,""text"":""2009"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":252,""end"":257,""text"":""eight"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":292,""end"":296,""text"":""2025"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":298,""end"":306,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":308,""end"":313,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":315,""end"":326,""text"":""Afghanistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":328,""end"":337,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":339,""end"":346,""text"":""England"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":348,""end"":359,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":361,""end"":373,""text"":""South Africa"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":379,""end"":389,""text"":""Bangladesh"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":420,""end"":429,""text"":""Sri Lanka"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":434,""end"":445,""text"":""West Indies"",""labels"":[""GPE""]}]",122.105,"The ICC Champions Trophy returns after eight years, with defending champion Pakistan facing New Zealand in Karachi on February 19. Initially launched in 1998 to support non-Test nations, early editions featured up to 12 teams. Since 2009, only the top eight ICC-ranked teams participate. For 2025, Pakistan, India, Afghanistan, Australia, England, New Zealand, South Africa, and Bangladesh qualified, while past winners Sri Lanka and West Indies missed out.","2025-02-23T11:47:40.611736Z"
5,"1","2025-02-23T11:49:53.286479Z",3,"[{""start"":0,""end"":12,""text"":""South Africa"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":28,""end"":34,""text"":""second"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":60,""end"":63,""text"":""ICC"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":64,""end"":85,""text"":""Champions Trophy 2025"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":103,""end"":114,""text"":""Afghanistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":118,""end"":125,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":129,""end"":135,""text"":""Friday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":141,""end"":148,""text"":""Proteas"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":197,""end"":201,""text"":""1998"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":219,""end"":230,""text"":""West Indies"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":245,""end"":257,""text"":""Temba Bavuma"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":263,""end"":276,""text"":""Tony de Zorzi"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":278,""end"":290,""text"":""Marco Jansen"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":292,""end"":308,""text"":""Heinrich Klaasen"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":310,""end"":324,""text"":""Keshav Maharaj"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":326,""end"":339,""text"":""Aiden Markram"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":341,""end"":353,""text"":""David Miller"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":355,""end"":367,""text"":""Wiaan Mulder"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":369,""end"":380,""text"":""Lungi Ngidi"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":382,""end"":395,""text"":""Kagiso Rabada"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":397,""end"":411,""text"":""Ryan Rickelton"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":413,""end"":427,""text"":""Tabraiz Shamsi"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":429,""end"":443,""text"":""Tristan Stubbs"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":445,""end"":466,""text"":""Rassie van der Dussen"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":468,""end"":480,""text"":""Corbin Bosch"",""labels"":[""PER""]}]",129.528,"South Africa will bid for a second title when it begins its ICC Champions Trophy 2025 campaign against Afghanistan in Karachi on Friday. The Proteas won the tournament in the inaugural edition, in 1998, after they beat West Indies in the final. Temba Bavuma (c), Tony de Zorzi, Marco Jansen, Heinrich Klaasen, Keshav Maharaj, Aiden Markram, David Miller, Wiaan Mulder, Lungi Ngidi, Kagiso Rabada, Ryan Rickelton, Tabraiz Shamsi, Tristan Stubbs, Rassie van der Dussen, Corbin Bosch.","2025-02-23T11:49:53.286500Z"
6,"1","2025-02-23T11:52:11.833359Z",4,"[{""start"":0,""end"":10,""text"":""Bangladesh"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":29,""end"":50,""text"":""Champions Trophy 2025"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":25,""end"":28,""text"":""ICC"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":86,""end"":91,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":95,""end"":100,""text"":""Dubai"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":104,""end"":112,""text"":""Thursday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":114,""end"":124,""text"":""Bangladesh"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":170,""end"":174,""text"":""2017"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":230,""end"":235,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":237,""end"":258,""text"":""Nazmul Hossain Shanto"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":264,""end"":277,""text"":""Soumya Sarkar"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":279,""end"":291,""text"":""Tanzid Hasan"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":293,""end"":306,""text"":""Tawhid Hridoy"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":308,""end"":323,""text"":""Mushfiqur Rahim"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":325,""end"":337,""text"":""Mahmud Ullah"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":339,""end"":353,""text"":""Jaker Ali Anik"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":355,""end"":373,""text"":""Mehidy Hasan Miraz"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":375,""end"":389,""text"":""Rishad Hossain"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":391,""end"":403,""text"":""Taskin Ahmed"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":405,""end"":422,""text"":""Mustafizur Rahman"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":424,""end"":443,""text"":""Parvez Hossain Emon"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":445,""end"":456,""text"":""Nasum Ahmed"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":458,""end"":476,""text"":""Tanzim Hasan Sakib"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":478,""end"":488,""text"":""Nahid Rana"",""labels"":[""PER""]}]",121.046,"Bangladesh will gets its ICC Champions Trophy 2025 campaign underway when it takes on India in Dubai on Thursday. Bangladeshs best performance in the competition came in 2017, when it qualified for the semifinal, where it lost to India. Nazmul Hossain Shanto (c), Soumya Sarkar, Tanzid Hasan, Tawhid Hridoy, Mushfiqur Rahim, Mahmud Ullah, Jaker Ali Anik, Mehidy Hasan Miraz, Rishad Hossain, Taskin Ahmed, Mustafizur Rahman, Parvez Hossain Emon, Nasum Ahmed, Tanzim Hasan Sakib, Nahid Rana","2025-02-23T11:52:11.833382Z"
7,"1","2025-02-23T11:54:11.007582Z",5,"[{""start"":5,""end"":13,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":29,""end"":45,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":25,""end"":28,""text"":""ICC"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":63,""end"":72,""text"":""Wednesday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":81,""end"":92,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":96,""end"":103,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":109,""end"":113,""text"":""2017"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":128,""end"":142,""text"":""Sarfaraz Ahmed"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":183,""end"":188,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":214,""end"":229,""text"":""Mohammad Rizwan"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":273,""end"":276,""text"":""ICC"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":284,""end"":299,""text"":""Mohammad Rizwan"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":305,""end"":315,""text"":""Babar Azam"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":317,""end"":329,""text"":""Fakhar Zaman"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":331,""end"":344,""text"":""Kamran Ghulam"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":346,""end"":358,""text"":""Saud Shakeel"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":360,""end"":372,""text"":""Tayyab Tahir"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":374,""end"":387,""text"":""Faheem Ashraf"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":389,""end"":402,""text"":""Khushdil Shah"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":404,""end"":419,""text"":""Salman Ali Agha"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":421,""end"":431,""text"":""Usman Khan"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":433,""end"":444,""text"":""Abrar Ahmed"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":446,""end"":456,""text"":""Haris Rauf"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":458,""end"":474,""text"":""Mohammad Hasnain"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":476,""end"":487,""text"":""Naseem Shah"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":489,""end"":508,""text"":""Shaheen Shah Afridi"",""labels"":[""PER""]}]",117.336,"Host Pakistan begins its ICC Champions Trophy title defense on Wednesday against New Zealand in Karachi. The 2017 triumph under Sarfaraz Ahmed remains its only title, secured against India in the final. This time, Mohammad Rizwan leads the side in front of home fans at an ICC event. Mohammad Rizwan (c), Babar Azam, Fakhar Zaman, Kamran Ghulam, Saud Shakeel, Tayyab Tahir, Faheem Ashraf, Khushdil Shah, Salman Ali Agha, Usman Khan, Abrar Ahmed, Haris Rauf, Mohammad Hasnain, Naseem Shah, Shaheen Shah Afridi.","2025-02-23T11:54:11.007611Z"
8,"1","2025-02-23T11:56:29.998294Z",6,"[{""start"":0,""end"":7,""text"":""England"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":54,""end"":57,""text"":""ICC"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":58,""end"":74,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":94,""end"":98,""text"":""2025"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":116,""end"":125,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":129,""end"":136,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":140,""end"":151,""text"":""February 26"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":153,""end"":168,""text"":""The Three Lions"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":180,""end"":189,""text"":""runner-up"",""labels"":[""ORDINAL""]},{""start"":190,""end"":195,""text"":""twice"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":200,""end"":204,""text"":""2013"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":209,""end"":213,""text"":""2004"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":242,""end"":249,""text"":""England"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":295,""end"":299,""text"":""2017"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":304,""end"":308,""text"":""2009"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":310,""end"":321,""text"":""Jos Buttler"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":327,""end"":339,""text"":""Jofra Archer"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":341,""end"":353,""text"":""Gus Atkinson"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":355,""end"":365,""text"":""Tom Banton"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":367,""end"":378,""text"":""Harry Brook"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":380,""end"":393,""text"":""Brydon Carse,"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":394,""end"":405,""text"":""Ben Duckett"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":407,""end"":420,""text"":""Jamie Overton"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":422,""end"":433,""text"":""Jamie Smith"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":435,""end"":451,""text"":""Liam Livingstone"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":453,""end"":464,""text"":""Adil Rashid"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":466,""end"":474,""text"":""Joe Root"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":476,""end"":489,""text"":""Saqib Mahmood"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":491,""end"":500,""text"":""Phil Salt"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":502,""end"":511,""text"":""Mark Wood"",""labels"":[""PER""]}]",136.445,"England will hope it can finally get its hands on the ICC Champions Trophy when it begins the 2025 campaign against Australia in Karachi on February 26. The Three Lions have ended runner-up twice, in 2013 and 2004  the two editions played in England. The side has also reached the semifinals in 2017 and 2009. Jos Buttler (c), Jofra Archer, Gus Atkinson, Tom Banton, Harry Brook, Brydon Carse, Ben Duckett, Jamie Overton, Jamie Smith, Liam Livingstone, Adil Rashid, Joe Root, Saqib Mahmood, Phil Salt, Mark Wood.","2025-02-23T11:56:29.998314Z"
9,"1","2025-02-23T11:58:46.041029Z",7,"[{""start"":321,""end"":337,""text"":""Mitchell Santner"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":343,""end"":360,""text"":""Michael Bracewell"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":362,""end"":374,""text"":""Mark Chapman"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":376,""end"":388,""text"":""Devon Conway"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":390,""end"":405,""text"":""Lockie Ferguson"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":407,""end"":417,""text"":""Matt Henry"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":419,""end"":429,""text"":""Tom Latham"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":431,""end"":445,""text"":""Daryl Mitchell"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":447,""end"":459,""text"":""Will ORourke"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":461,""end"":475,""text"":""Glenn Phillips"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":477,""end"":492,""text"":""Rachin Ravindra"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":494,""end"":506,""text"":""Nathan Smith"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":508,""end"":523,""text"":""Kane Williamson"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":525,""end"":535,""text"":""Will Young"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":537,""end"":548,""text"":""Jacob Duffy"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":0,""end"":11,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":20,""end"":26,""text"":""second"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":42,""end"":45,""text"":""ICC"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":46,""end"":62,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":76,""end"":79,""text"":""ICC"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":80,""end"":88,""text"":""Knockout"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":161,""end"":170,""text"":""runner-up"",""labels"":[""ORDINAL""]},{""start"":185,""end"":189,""text"":""2009"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":209,""end"":218,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":233,""end"":247,""text"":""The Black Caps"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":307,""end"":310,""text"":""two"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]}]",123.722,"New Zealand won the second edition of the ICC Champions Trophy, then called ICC Knockout, but has had to wait to get its hands on the trophy since. It managed a runner-up finish in the 2009 edition, losing to Australia in the final. The Black Caps have failed to make it past the group stage since the last two editions. Mitchell Santner (c), Michael Bracewell, Mark Chapman, Devon Conway, Lockie Ferguson, Matt Henry, Tom Latham, Daryl Mitchell, Will ORourke, Glenn Phillips, Rachin Ravindra, Nathan Smith, Kane Williamson, Will Young, Jacob Duffy.","2025-02-23T11:58:46.041050Z"
10,"1","2025-02-23T12:00:14.712011Z",8,"[{""start"":0,""end"":16,""text"":""Less than a week"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":59,""end"":69,""text"":""tri-series"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":71,""end"":79,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":84,""end"":95,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":114,""end"":139,""text"":""ICC Champions Trophy 2025"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":143,""end"":152,""text"":""Wednesday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":160,""end"":181,""text"":""National Bank Stadium"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":185,""end"":192,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":205,""end"":210,""text"":""Kiwis"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":244,""end"":248,""text"":""week"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":286,""end"":295,""text"":""Wednesday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":332,""end"":348,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":382,""end"":390,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":415,""end"":430,""text"":""Mohammad Rizwan"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":446,""end"":456,""text"":""ODI series"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":465,""end"":474,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":479,""end"":491,""text"":""South Africa"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":493,""end"":499,""text"":""Rizwan"",""labels"":[""PER""]}]",87.067,"Less than a week after squaring up against each other in a tri-series, Pakistan and New Zealand will kick off the ICC Champions Trophy 2025 on Wednesday at the National Bank Stadium in Karachi. Though the Kiwis trounced the host twice within a week, it will be the high-stakes clash on Wednesday they would want to win to get their Champions Trophy campaign to a winning start. For Pakistan, life under new captain Mohammad Rizwan has begun with ODI series wins in Australia and South Africa. Rizwan would want the side to carry that momentum and begin its title defence in style.","2025-02-23T12:00:14.712033Z"
11,"1","2025-02-23T12:02:09.480125Z",9,"[{""start"":0,""end"":5,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":21,""end"":26,""text"":""third"",""labels"":[""ORDINAL""]},{""start"":52,""end"":77,""text"":""ICC Champions Trophy 2025"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":95,""end"":105,""text"":""Bangladesh"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":109,""end"":114,""text"":""Dubai"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":118,""end"":126,""text"":""Thursday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":128,""end"":133,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":156,""end"":160,""text"":""2002"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":180,""end"":189,""text"":""Sri Lanka"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":228,""end"":236,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":195,""end"":199,""text"":""2013"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":253,""end"":257,""text"":""2017"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":282,""end"":291,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":304,""end"":324,""text"":""ICC Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":346,""end"":357,""text"":""Men in Blue"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":359,""end"":371,""text"":""Rohit Sharma"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":377,""end"":389,""text"":""Shubman Gill"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":396,""end"":407,""text"":""Virat Kohli"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":409,""end"":421,""text"":""Shreyas Iyer"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":423,""end"":431,""text"":""KL Rahul"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":438,""end"":450,""text"":""Rishabh Pant"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":457,""end"":470,""text"":""Hardik Pandya"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":472,""end"":482,""text"":""Axar Patel"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":484,""end"":501,""text"":""Washington Sundar"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":503,""end"":516,""text"":""Kuldeep Yadav"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":518,""end"":530,""text"":""Harshit Rana"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":532,""end"":546,""text"":""Mohammed Shami"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":548,""end"":562,""text"":""Arshdeep Singh"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":564,""end"":579,""text"":""Ravindra Jadeja"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":581,""end"":600,""text"":""Varun Chakaravarthy"",""labels"":[""PER""]}]",112.738,"India will bid for a third title when it begins its ICC Champions Trophy 2025 campaign against Bangladesh in Dubai on Thursday. India won the tournament in 2002 (joint-winner with Sri Lanka) and 2013, before losing to archrival Pakistan in the final in 2017. Only two-time champion Australia has won the ICC Champions Trophy as many times as the Men in Blue. Rohit Sharma (c), Shubman Gill (vc), Virat Kohli, Shreyas Iyer, KL Rahul (wk), Rishabh Pant (wk), Hardik Pandya, Axar Patel, Washington Sundar, Kuldeep Yadav, Harshit Rana, Mohammed Shami, Arshdeep Singh, Ravindra Jadeja, Varun Chakaravarthy.","2025-02-23T12:02:09.480152Z"
12,"1","2025-02-23T12:03:56.964765Z",10,"[{""start"":4,""end"":8,""text"":""2025"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":9,""end"":29,""text"":""ICC Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":47,""end"":58,""text"":""February 19"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":65,""end"":73,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":81,""end"":92,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":96,""end"":103,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":109,""end"":119,""text"":""tournament"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":133,""end"":138,""text"":""eight"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":158,""end"":161,""text"":""two"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":172,""end"":176,""text"":""four"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":189,""end"":191,""text"":""12"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":286,""end"":294,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":361,""end"":366,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":368,""end"":377,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":379,""end"":391,""text"":""South Africa"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":393,""end"":404,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":406,""end"":413,""text"":""England"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":415,""end"":425,""text"":""Bangladesh"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":431,""end"":442,""text"":""Afghanistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":500,""end"":518,""text"":""2023 ODI World Cup"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":520,""end"":531,""text"":""Afghanistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":593,""end"":602,""text"":""Sri Lanka"",""labels"":[""GPE""]}]",102.273,"The 2025 ICC Champions Trophy will commence on February 19, with Pakistan facing New Zealand in Karachi. The tournament will feature eight teams divided into two groups of four. A total of 12 group-stage matches will be played, followed by the semifinals and final. As the host nation, Pakistan secured automatic qualification, while the remaining seven teams  India, Australia, South Africa, New Zealand, England, Bangladesh, and Afghanistan  earned their spots by finishing in the top seven at the 2023 ODI World Cup. Afghanistan will make its debut in the tournament, while former champion Sri Lanka failed to qualify.","2025-02-23T12:03:56.964786Z"
13,"1","2025-02-23T12:05:50.929774Z",11,"[{""start"":4,""end"":29,""text"":""2025 ICC Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":47,""end"":58,""text"":""February 19"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":65,""end"":73,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":81,""end"":92,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":96,""end"":103,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":109,""end"":119,""text"":""tournament"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":146,""end"":154,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":159,""end"":162,""text"":""UAE"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":199,""end"":204,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":212,""end"":232,""text"":""The Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":246,""end"":251,""text"":""eight"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":272,""end"":275,""text"":""two"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":286,""end"":290,""text"":""four"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":308,""end"":310,""text"":""12"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":427,""end"":438,""text"":""February 20"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":440,""end"":451,""text"":""February 23"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":456,""end"":463,""text"":""March 2"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":496,""end"":503,""text"":""March 4"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":508,""end"":509,""text"":""5"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":536,""end"":543,""text"":""March 9"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":578,""end"":584,""text"":""Lahore"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":643,""end"":648,""text"":""Dubai"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":593,""end"":598,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]}]",111.314,"The 2025 ICC Champions Trophy will kick off on February 19, with Pakistan facing New Zealand in Karachi. The tournament will be jointly hosted by Pakistan and UAE, with the latter set to host all of Indias games The Champions Trophy will feature eight teams, divided into two groups of four each. A total of 12 group-stage matches will be played, followed by the semifinals and final.  India will play its group-stage games on February 20, February 23 and March 2. The semifinals will be held on March 4 and 5, followed by the final on March 9. The summit clash will be held in Lahore, unless India qualifies, in which case it will be held in Dubai.","2025-02-23T12:05:50.929806Z"
14,"1","2025-02-23T12:07:03.407583Z",12,"[{""start"":37,""end"":67,""text"":""ICC Mens Champions Trophy 2025"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":126,""end"":143,""text"":""Abdullah Siddiqui"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":160,""end"":171,""text"":""Adnan Dhool"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":176,""end"":190,""text"":""Asfandyar Asad"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":209,""end"":219,""text"":""Atif Aslam"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":318,""end"":321,""text"":""ICC"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":331,""end"":339,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":348,""end"":351,""text"":""UAE"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":451,""end"":460,""text"":""Pakistans"",""labels"":[""GPE""]}]",54.058,"Q: What is the official song for the ICC Mens Champions Trophy 2025? A: The official song is Jeeto Baazi Khel Ke, produced by Abdullah Siddiqui, with lyrics by Adnan Dhool and Asfandyar Asad, and performed by Atif Aslam. Q: What does the song represent? A: The song captures the passion and excitement of the upcoming ICC event in Pakistan and the UAE, celebrating the spirit of cricket. Q: What is featured in the music video? A: The video showcases Pakistans rich culture, highlighting vibrant streets, markets, and stadiums, while capturing the energy of cricket fans worldwide. Q: Where can the song be streamed? A: Jeeto Baazi Khel Ke is available on popular audio streaming platforms globally.","2025-02-23T12:07:03.407602Z"
15,"1","2025-02-23T12:09:28.353544Z",13,"[{""start"":21,""end"":41,""text"":""ICC Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":42,""end"":46,""text"":""2025"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":80,""end"":89,""text"":""Wednesday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":129,""end"":140,""text"":""February 19"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":173,""end"":190,""text"":""February 14 to 17"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":196,""end"":224,""text"":""Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB)"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":288,""end"":299,""text"":""February 14"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":301,""end"":312,""text"":""Shadab Khan"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":323,""end"":331,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":349,""end"":360,""text"":""Afghanistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":364,""end"":370,""text"":""Lahore"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":375,""end"":386,""text"":""17 February"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":428,""end"":435,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":440,""end"":446,""text"":""Dubai."",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":447,""end"":464,""text"":""Mohammad Hurraira"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":492,""end"":504,""text"":""South Africa"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":508,""end"":515,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":523,""end"":537,""text"":""Mohammad Haris"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":565,""end"":575,""text"":""Bangladesh"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":586,""end"":597,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":579,""end"":584,""text"":""Dubai"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":602,""end"":613,""text"":""Afghanistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":652,""end"":659,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":663,""end"":674,""text"":""February 16"",""labels"":[""DATE""]}]",120.698,"The schedule for the ICC Champions Trophy 2025 warm-up matches was announced on Wednesday. While the main tournament begins from February 19, the warm-ups will be held from February 14 to 17. The Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB) named three squads that will participate in these fixtures. On February 14, Shadab Khan will lead Pakistan Shaheens against Afghanistan in Lahore. On 17 February, two Shaheens teams will be in action in Karachi and Dubai. Mohammad Hurraira will lead Shaheens against South Africa in Karachi, while Mohammad Haris will lead Shaheens against Bangladesh in Dubai. New Zealand and Afghanistan will also play out a warm-up match in Karachi on February 16. All the warm-up matches will be day-night fixtures.","2025-02-23T12:09:28.353574Z"
16,"1","2025-02-23T12:12:33.958491Z",14,"[{""start"":4,""end"":29,""text"":""2025 ICC Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":40,""end"":51,""text"":""February 19"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":58,""end"":66,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":74,""end"":85,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":89,""end"":96,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":98,""end"":103,""text"":""Eight"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":126,""end"":129,""text"":""two"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":140,""end"":144,""text"":""four"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":154,""end"":156,""text"":""12"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":216,""end"":226,""text"":""Sri Lankan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":233,""end"":249,""text"":""Farveez Maharoof"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":299,""end"":315,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":349,""end"":353,""text"":""6\/14"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":362,""end"":373,""text"":""West Indies"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":377,""end"":381,""text"":""2006"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":389,""end"":406,""text"":""Brabourne Stadium"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":408,""end"":414,""text"":""Mumbai"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":441,""end"":443,""text"":""80"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":445,""end"":454,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":456,""end"":470,""text"":""Josh Hazlewood"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":506,""end"":509,""text"":""six"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":568,""end"":579,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":587,""end"":591,""text"":""2017"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":632,""end"":638,""text"":""Indian"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":646,""end"":662,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":673,""end"":688,""text"":""Ravindra Jadeja"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":702,""end"":706,""text"":""5\/36"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":715,""end"":727,""text"":""West Indies "",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":730,""end"":734,""text"":""2013"",""labels"":[""DATE""]}]",180.981,"The 2025 ICC Champions Trophy begins on February 19, with Pakistan facing New Zealand in Karachi. Eight teams will compete in two groups of four, playing 12 group-stage matches, followed by the semifinals and final. Sri Lankan pacer Farveez Maharoof holds the record for the best bowling figures in Champions Trophy history. His remarkable spell of 6/14 against West Indies in 2006 at the Brabourne Stadium, Mumbai, skittled it out for just 80. Australias Josh Hazlewood is the only other bowler to take a six-wicket haul in the tournament, achieving the feat against New Zealand in the 2017 edition. The best bowling figures by an Indian in the Champions Trophy belong to Ravindra Jadeja, who claimed 5/36 against West Indies in 2013.","2025-02-23T12:12:33.958518Z"
17,"1","2025-02-23T12:15:01.827554Z",15,"[{""start"":23,""end"":42,""text"":""Varun Chakaravarthy"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":61,""end"":66,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":0,""end"":6,""text"":""Indian"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":74,""end"":76,""text"":""15"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":107,""end"":132,""text"":""ICC Champions Trophy 2025"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":153,""end"":169,""text"":""Yashasvi Jaiswal"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":224,""end"":229,""text"":""Varun"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":248,""end"":257,""text"":""ODI debut"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":266,""end"":273,""text"":""England"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":281,""end"":287,""text"":""second"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":301,""end"":315,""text"":""ongoing series"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":395,""end"":406,""text"":""T20I series"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":425,""end"":427,""text"":""14"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":444,""end"":453,""text"":""ODI debut"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":455,""end"":460,""text"":""Varun"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":485,""end"":492,""text"":""English"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":500,""end"":509,""text"":""Phil Salt"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":542,""end"":544,""text"":""54"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":548,""end"":550,""text"":""10"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":562,""end"":564,""text"":""33"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":597,""end"":624,""text"":""Vijay Hazare Trophy 2024-25"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":642,""end"":644,""text"":""18"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":657,""end"":667,""text"":""Tamil Nadu"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":697,""end"":702,""text"":""12.16"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":709,""end"":714,""text"":""eight"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":747,""end"":758,""text"":""February 19"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":762,""end"":769,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":781,""end"":789,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":797,""end"":808,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]}]",144.999,"Indian mystery spinner Varun Chakaravarthy has been named in Indias final 15-member squad for the upcoming ICC Champions Trophy 2025. He replaces batter Yashasvi Jaiswal, who was initially included in the provisional squad. Varun recently made his ODI debut against England in the second match of the ongoing series. This opportunity came on the back of his strong performances in the preceding T20I series, where he claimed 14 wickets. On his ODI debut, Varun picked up the wicket of English opener Phil Salt and returned figures of one for 54 in 10 overs. The 33-year-old also had an impressive Vijay Hazare Trophy 2024-25 campaign, taking 18 wickets for Tamil Nadu at an outstanding average of 12.16.  The eight-nation tournament will begin on February 19 in Karachi, with host Pakistan facing New Zealand in the opening match.","2025-02-23T12:15:01.827589Z"
18,"1","2025-02-23T12:17:03.533151Z",16,"[{""start"":14,""end"":27,""text"":""Anrich Nortje"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":0,""end"":12,""text"":""South Africa"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":54,""end"":74,""text"":""ICC Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":154,""end"":160,""text"":""Nortje"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":174,""end"":186,""text"":""South Africa"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":197,""end"":203,""text"":""Monday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":209,""end"":211,""text"":""48"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":326,""end"":337,""text"":""Afghanistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":341,""end"":348,""text"":""Feb. 21"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":350,""end"":357,""text"":""England"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":362,""end"":371,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":394,""end"":401,""text"":""Nortjes"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":457,""end"":471,""text"":""Gerald Coetzee"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":532,""end"":534,""text"":""18"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":556,""end"":569,""text"":""Kwena Maphaka"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":589,""end"":595,""text"":""Nortje"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":671,""end"":681,""text"":""test match"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":688,""end"":698,""text"":""March 2023"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":733,""end"":755,""text"":""September of that year"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":705,""end"":726,""text"":""one-day international"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":800,""end"":818,""text"":""Twenty20 World Cup"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":826,""end"":838,""text"":""South Africa"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":860,""end"":865,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]}]",117.289,"South Africas Anrich Nortje has been ruled out of the ICC Champions Trophy with a back injury, the latest in a long line of setbacks for the fast bowler. Nortje was named in South Africas squad on Monday, but 48 hours on, officials have said he will not recover in time from a back problem ahead of the Group B opener against Afghanistan on Feb. 21. England and Australia are also in the pool. Nortjes replacement will be named at a later date, with seamer Gerald Coetzee a possible pick after he recovered from a groin strain. The 18-year-old fast bowler Kwena Maphaka is another option. Nortje has had persistent injury issues over several seasons. He has not played a test match since March 2023 and a one-day international since September of that year. He was fit enough to feature in last years Twenty20 World Cup, where South Africa lost in the final to India.","2025-02-23T12:17:03.533170Z"
19,"1","2025-02-23T12:18:59.643594Z",17,"[{""start"":0,""end"":15,""text"":""Allah Ghazanfar"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":51,""end"":72,""text"":""Champions Trophy 2025"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":92,""end"":123,""text"":""Afghanistan Cricket Board (ACB)"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":152,""end"":161,""text"":""Wednesday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":163,""end"":174,""text"":""Afghanistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":206,""end"":218,""text"":""AM Ghazanfar"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":246,""end"":266,""text"":""ICC Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":357,""end"":360,""text"":""ACB"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":373,""end"":375,""text"":""18"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":437,""end"":448,""text"":""Afghanistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":458,""end"":466,""text"":""Zimbabwe"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":481,""end"":495,""text"":""Mumbai Indians"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":533,""end"":537,""text"":""4.80"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":545,""end"":554,""text"":""Ghazanfar"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":594,""end"":615,""text"":""Indian Premier League"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":574,""end"":578,""text"":""2025"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":666,""end"":677,""text"":""four months"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":679,""end"":694,""text"":""Nangyal Kharoti"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":775,""end"":791,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":797,""end"":800,""text"":""ACB"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":848,""end"":864,""text"":""Mujeeb Ur Rahman"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":904,""end"":918,""text"":""50-over format"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]}]",110.974,"Allah Ghazanfar has been ruled out of the upcoming Champions Trophy 2025 due to injury, the Afghanistan Cricket Board (ACB) announced in a statement on Wednesday. Afghanistans young spin-bowling sensation, AM Ghazanfar, has been ruled out of the ICC Champions Trophy due to a fracture in the L4 vertebra, specifically in the left pars interarticularis, the ACB stated. The 18-year-old spinner is said to have sustained the injury during Afghanistans tour of Zimbabwe. In a blow to Mumbai Indians, which acquired the youngster for Rs 4.80 crore, Ghazanfar will also miss the 2025 edition of the Indian Premier League, as his injury will sideline him for a minimum of four months. Nangyal Kharoti, who was part of the reserves pool, has been promoted to the main squad for the Champions Trophy, the ACB added. The cricketing body also confirmed that Mujeeb Ur Rahman will continue to be unavailable in the 50-over format until he has fully recovered.","2025-02-23T12:18:59.643615Z"
20,"1","2025-02-23T12:20:49.335914Z",18,"[{""start"":0,""end"":14,""text"":""Mitchell Marsh"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":50,""end"":75,""text"":""ICC Mens Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":227,""end"":229,""text"":""73"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":163,""end"":175,""text"":""Beau Webster"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":109,""end"":114,""text"":""Marsh"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":184,""end"":187,""text"":""SCG"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":202,""end"":207,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":238,""end"":243,""text"":""seven"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":294,""end"":316,""text"":""Border-Gavaskar Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":342,""end"":345,""text"":""BBL"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":335,""end"":341,""text"":""single"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":354,""end"":363,""text"":""January 7"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":386,""end"":391,""text"":""three"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":424,""end"":440,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":442,""end"":447,""text"":""Marsh"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":477,""end"":480,""text"":""IPL"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":492,""end"":512,""text"":""Lucknow Super Giants"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":526,""end"":529,""text"":""LSG"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":554,""end"":557,""text"":""3.4"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":576,""end"":588,""text"":""mega auction"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":590,""end"":604,""text"":""Mitchell Marsh"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":640,""end"":665,""text"":""ICC Mens Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":787,""end"":790,""text"":""NSP"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":917,""end"":928,""text"":""February 12"",""labels"":[""DATE""]}]",100.961,"Mitchell Marsh has been ruled out of the upcoming ICC Mens Champions Trophy due to a persistent back injury. Marsh has had a tough season, losing his Test spot to Beau Webster for the SCG match against India after scoring just 73 runs in seven innings and playing a limited bowling role in the Border-Gavaskar Trophy. He featured in a single BBL game on January 7 but skipped the final three matches to recover ahead of the Champions Trophy. Marshs injury could also leave his IPL stint with Lucknow Super Giants in jeopardy. LSG had acquired him for Rs 3.4 crore at the last mega auction. Mitchell Marsh has been ruled out of the upcoming ICC Mens Champions Trophy with ongoing lower back pain and dysfunction, the statement said. His lower back pain flared in recent weeks leading the NSP to make the longer term decision for Marsh to complete a more extended period of rehabilitation. The selectors have time till February 12 to name a replacement.","2025-02-23T12:20:49.335932Z"
21,"1","2025-02-23T12:22:38.811627Z",19,"[{""start"":0,""end"":14,""text"":""Mitchell Starc"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":47,""end"":63,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":68,""end"":90,""text"":""Cricket Australia (CA)"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":124,""end"":139,""text"":"" ICC tournament"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":143,""end"":152,""text"":""Wednesday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":187,""end"":192,""text"":""Starc"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":194,""end"":205,""text"":""Pat Cummins"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":211,""end"":225,""text"":""Josh Hazlewood"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":179,""end"":183,""text"":""trio"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":288,""end"":299,""text"":""February 19"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":303,""end"":311,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":313,""end"":318,""text"":""Starc"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":460,""end"":464,""text"":""four"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":478,""end"":488,""text"":""Sri Lankas"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":518,""end"":528,""text"":""final Test"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":532,""end"":537,""text"":""Galle"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":541,""end"":543,""text"":""CA"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":584,""end"":589,""text"":""Mitch"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":614,""end"":616,""text"":""CA"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":643,""end"":656,""text"":""George Bailey"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":752,""end"":767,""text"":""Spencer Johnson"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":769,""end"":781,""text"":""Nathan Ellis"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":783,""end"":794,""text"":""Sean Abbott"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":799,""end"":812,""text"":""Ben Dwarshuis"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":874,""end"":890,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":892,""end"":901,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":923,""end"":939,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":952,""end"":956,""text"":""2009"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":943,""end"":947,""text"":""2006"",""labels"":[""DATE""]}]",107.795,"Mitchell Starc has withdrawn from the upcoming Champions Trophy, as Cricket Australia (CA) announced its final squad for the ICC tournament on Wednesday. This means that the pace trio of Starc, Pat Cummins, and Josh Hazlewood will be absent from the competition, which is set to begin on February 19 in Pakistan. Starc, who will not be commenting about his decision and has asked for privacy, looked to be in discomfort with a left ankle issue in bowling just four overs during Sri Lankas second innings of last weeks final Test at Galle, a CA release said. We understand and respect Mitchs decision, chair of the CAs national selection panel George Bailey said. The absence of the high-profile pace trio has opened the door for next-generation quicks Spencer Johnson, Nathan Ellis, Sean Abbott and Ben Dwarshuis who have been named in Australias final 15-man squad for the Champions Trophy. Australia has twice lifted the Champions Trophy in 2006 and 2009.","2025-02-23T12:22:38.811648Z"
22,"1","2025-02-23T12:25:06.851023Z",20,"[{""start"":4,""end"":39,""text"":""International Cricket Council (ICC)"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":53,""end"":64,""text"":""December 19"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":74,""end"":78,""text"":""2025"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":79,""end"":95,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":182,""end"":190,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":224,""end"":235,""text"":""February 19"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":262,""end"":267,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":320,""end"":323,""text"":""ICC"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":350,""end"":355,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":360,""end"":368,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":405,""end"":415,""text"":""ICC Events"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":427,""end"":436,""text"":""2024-2027"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":595,""end"":599,""text"":""2008"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":606,""end"":611,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":626,""end"":634,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":635,""end"":647,""text"":""16 years ago"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":658,""end"":666,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":681,""end"":686,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":695,""end"":726,""text"":""2023 ICC Mens Cricket World Cup"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":728,""end"":756,""text"":""Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB)"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":766,""end"":778,""text"":""Mohsin Naqvi"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":935,""end"":946,""text"":""Afghanistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":948,""end"":957,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":959,""end"":969,""text"":""Bangladesh"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":971,""end"":978,""text"":""England"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":980,""end"":985,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":987,""end"":998,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":1004,""end"":1016,""text"":""South Africa"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":1034,""end"":1042,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":905,""end"":921,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":894,""end"":899,""text"":""eight"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]}]",143.536,"The International Cricket Council (ICC) confirmed on December 19 that the 2025 Champions Trophy will be staged using a hybrid model or at a neutral venue. Scheduled to take place in Pakistan, the tournament, set to begin on February 19, faced uncertainty due to Indias refusal to travel to the host nation. However, the ICC in a release has now said India and Pakistan matches hosted by either country at ICC Events during the 2024-2027 rights cycle will be played at a neutral venue. Political tensions between the two countries have prevented bilateral cricket outside major tournaments since 2008, with India last visiting Pakistan 16 years ago. However, Pakistan did travel to India for the 2023 ICC Mens Cricket World Cup. Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB) chairman Mohsin Naqvi had previously opposed the hybrid hosting model, which would see Indias matches played in a different country. The eight-team Champions Trophy will feature Afghanistan, Australia, Bangladesh, England, India, New Zealand, and South Africa, alongside hosts Pakistan.","2025-02-23T12:25:06.851042Z"
23,"1","2025-02-23T12:27:53.884548Z",21,"[{""start"":4,""end"":29,""text"":""ICC Champions Trophy 2025"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":44,""end"":55,""text"":""February 19"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":82,""end"":86,""text"":""four"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":116,""end"":124,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":136,""end"":146,""text"":""Dubai, UAE"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":148,""end"":155,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":157,""end"":163,""text"":""Lahore"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":169,""end"":179,""text"":""Rawalpindi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":201,""end"":209,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":217,""end"":222,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":250,""end"":255,""text"":""Dubai"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":415,""end"":443,""text"":""Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB)"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":474,""end"":479,""text"":""three"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":490,""end"":500,""text"":""January 28"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":550,""end"":560,""text"":""February 3"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":520,""end"":525,""text"":""Dubai"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":657,""end"":677,""text"":""Global Sports Travel"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":750,""end"":785,""text"":""Dubai International Cricket Stadium"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":797,""end"":804,""text"":""AED 250"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":806,""end"":815,""text"":""INR 6,000"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":869,""end"":889,""text"":""AED 500 (INR 12,000)"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":894,""end"":902,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":961,""end"":982,""text"":""PKR 2,000 (INR 1,200)"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":1037,""end"":1056,""text"":""PKR 1,000 (INR 600)"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]}]",127.294,"The ICC Champions Trophy 2025 will begin on February 19, with matches held across four venues  three in host nation Pakistan and one in Dubai, UAE. Karachi, Lahore, and Rawalpindi will host matches in Pakistan, while India will play all its games in Dubai, including the semifinal and final (if qualified), due to security concerns. Tickets for all venues, including the semifinals, are available for purchase. The Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB) launched ticket sales for its three venues on January 28, while tickets for Dubai matches went on sale on February 3. The tickets can be bought through the Champions Trophy website. Tickets can also be booked via Global Sports Travel, an officially appointed agent for the tournament. Ticket prices at the Dubai International Cricket Stadium start from AED 250 (INR 6,000). Tickets for the Pakistan vs India match start from AED 500 (INR 12,000). In Pakistan, tickets for matches involving the host nation start from PKR 2,000 (INR 1,200), while tickets for non-Pakistan games are priced from PKR 1,000 (INR 600).","2025-02-23T12:27:53.884566Z"
24,"1","2025-02-23T12:30:17.848876Z",22,"[{""start"":844,""end"":855,""text"":""Steve Smith"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":862,""end"":872,""text"":""ean Abbott"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":874,""end"":884,""text"":""Alex Carey"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":886,""end"":899,""text"":""Ben Dwarshuis"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":901,""end"":913,""text"":""Nathan Ellis"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":915,""end"":933,""text"":""Jake Fraser-McGurk"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":935,""end"":947,""text"":""Aaron Hardie"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":949,""end"":960,""text"":""Travis Head"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":962,""end"":973,""text"":""Josh Inglis"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":975,""end"":990,""text"":""Spencer Johnson"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":992,""end"":1010,""text"":""Marnus Labuschagne"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1012,""end"":1025,""text"":""Glenn Maxwell"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1027,""end"":1041,""text"":""Tanveer Sangha"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1043,""end"":1056,""text"":""Matthew Short"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1058,""end"":1068,""text"":""Adam Zampa"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":11,""end"":21,""text"":""Australian"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":48,""end"":68,""text"":""ICC Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":42,""end"":47,""text"":""third"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":124,""end"":131,""text"":""England"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":135,""end"":141,""text"":""Lahore"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":145,""end"":156,""text"":""February 22"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":158,""end"":167,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":215,""end"":219,""text"":""2006"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":224,""end"":228,""text"":""2009"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":255,""end"":266,""text"":""Pat Cummins"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":292,""end"":305,""text"":""ODI World Cup"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":315,""end"":319,""text"":""2023"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":321,""end"":332,""text"":""Steve Smith"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":346,""end"":353,""text"":""Cummins"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":462,""end"":475,""text"":""ODI World Cup"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":477,""end"":486,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":540,""end"":560,""text"":""ICC Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":520,""end"":523,""text"":""two"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":590,""end"":594,""text"":""2013"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":599,""end"":603,""text"":""2017"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":772,""end"":776,""text"":""2009"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":708,""end"":717,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":791,""end"":802,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":806,""end"":815,""text"":""Centurion"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":830,""end"":836,""text"":""second"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]}]",139.003,"A depleted Australian team will vie for a third ICC Champions Trophy title when it kicks off its campaign against archrival England in Lahore on February 22. Australia, the only team to have won consecutive titles (2006 and 2009), will be without skipper Pat Cummins, who led the team to the ODI World Cup crown in 2023. Steve Smith will replace Cummins at the helm for the duration of the tournament. Though it is the most successful team in the history of the ODI World Cup, Australia has had a rough time in the last two editions of the ICC Champions Trophy. It exited the tournament in 2013 and 2017 in the group stage after a number of its matches were washed out due to inclement weather. As a result, Australia has been winless in the tournament since the final in 2009, when it beat New Zealand at Centurion to clinch its second title. Steve Smith (c), Sean Abbott, Alex Carey, Ben Dwarshuis, Nathan Ellis, Jake Fraser-McGurk, Aaron Hardie, Travis Head, Josh Inglis, Spencer Johnson, Marnus Labuschagne, Glenn Maxwell, Tanveer Sangha, Matthew Short, Adam Zampa.","2025-02-23T12:30:17.848902Z"
25,"1","2025-02-23T12:32:08.513183Z",23,"[{""start"":15,""end"":23,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":43,""end"":63,""text"":""ICC Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":67,""end"":74,""text"":""England"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":78,""end"":82,""text"":""2017"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":131,""end"":135,""text"":""2025"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":107,""end"":123,""text"":""opening ceremony"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":151,""end"":161,""text"":""tournament"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":165,""end"":171,""text"":""Lahore"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":173,""end"":187,""text"":""Sarfaraz Ahmed"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":220,""end"":235,""text"":""Mohammad Hafeez"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":237,""end"":247,""text"":""Wahab Riaz"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":249,""end"":262,""text"":""Mohammad Amir"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":264,""end"":274,""text"":""Imad Wasim"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":276,""end"":287,""text"":""Junaid Khan"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":289,""end"":298,""text"":""Azhar Ali"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":300,""end"":312,""text"":""Haris Sohail"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":326,""end"":334,""text"":""ceremony"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":338,""end"":344,""text"":""Sunday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":499,""end"":503,""text"":""2017"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":592,""end"":600,""text"":""Sarfaraz"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":607,""end"":615,""text"":""Sarfaraz"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":635,""end"":643,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":746,""end"":749,""text"":""ICC"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":964,""end"":972,""text"":""Sarfaraz"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":989,""end"":993,""text"":""2017"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":1008,""end"":1013,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]}]",108.91,"Members of the Pakistan squad that won the ICC Champions Trophy in England in 2017 were felicitated at the opening ceremony of the 2025 edition of the tournament in Lahore. Sarfaraz Ahmed, who was leading the team then, Mohammad Hafeez, Wahab Riaz, Mohammad Amir, Imad Wasim, Junaid Khan, Azhar Ali, Haris Sohail attended the ceremony on Sunday and they expressed confidence in the current teams ability to defend the title. Definitely our team is very capable of defending the title we won back in 2017. We have a good tight squad but it all depends on which players perform on a given day, Sarfaraz said. Sarfaraz also made it clear Pakistan would definitely enjoy the advantage of playing at home. It is after a long time we are hosting a big ICC event so I think the support of the people and the occasion will also inspire our players to give their best, he added. He said that it was up to the captain and management to create momentum in the dressing room. Sarfaraz also termed the 2017 final against India as his most memorable match. I can never forget that match.","2025-02-23T12:32:08.513207Z"
26,"1","2025-02-23T12:34:47.335991Z",24,"[{""start"":47,""end"":52,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":88,""end"":93,""text"":""Dubai"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":95,""end"":98,""text"":""UAE"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":116,""end"":137,""text"":""Champions Trophy 2025"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":143,""end"":178,""text"":""International Cricket Council (ICC)"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":192,""end"":198,""text"":""Sunday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":266,""end"":271,""text"":""today"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":349,""end"":360,""text"":""February 20"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":335,""end"":345,""text"":""Bangladesh"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":303,""end"":309,""text"":""Indias"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":440,""end"":448,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":450,""end"":461,""text"":""February 23"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":467,""end"":478,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":480,""end"":487,""text"":""March 2"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":494,""end"":497,""text"":""ICC"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":566,""end"":578,""text"":""semi-final 1"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":607,""end"":642,""text"":""Dubai International Cricket Stadium"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":646,""end"":653,""text"":""Tuesday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":655,""end"":662,""text"":""March 4"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":723,""end"":730,""text"":""March 9"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":816,""end"":821,""text"":""Dubai"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":836,""end"":839,""text"":""UAE"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":847,""end"":868,""text"":""Champions Trophy 2025"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":869,""end"":880,""text"":""February 20"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":883,""end"":888,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":892,""end"":902,""text"":""Bangladesh"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":905,""end"":932,""text"":""Dubai International Stadium"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":933,""end"":944,""text"":""February 23"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":947,""end"":952,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":956,""end"":964,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":967,""end"":994,""text"":""Dubai International Stadium"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":995,""end"":1003,""text"":""March 2 "",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":1005,""end"":1010,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":1014,""end"":1025,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":1028,""end"":1055,""text"":""Dubai International Stadium"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":1056,""end"":1063,""text"":""March 4"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":1066,""end"":1077,""text"":""Semifinal 1"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":1080,""end"":1107,""text"":""Dubai International Stadium"",""labels"":[""LOC""]}]",154.826,"Extra tickets have been made available for all India matches and the first semifinal in Dubai, UAE for the upcoming Champions Trophy 2025, the International Cricket Council (ICC) announced on Sunday. The sale for these tickets will begin at 12 PM GST or 1:30 PM IST today. Tickets will be available for Indias opening group match with Bangladesh on February 20, while there will also be tickets available for their games against arch-rival Pakistan (February 23) and New Zealand (March 2), the ICC said in a release. There will also be limited tickets available for semi-final 1 that will take place at the Dubai International Cricket Stadium on Tuesday, March 4, the release added. Tickets for the final - to be played on March 9 - will only be available for sale following the conclusion of the first semifinal in Dubai. Schedule for UAE leg of Champions Trophy 2025 February 20 - India vs Bangladesh - Dubai International Stadium February 23 - India vs Pakistan - Dubai International Stadium March 2 - India vs New Zealand - Dubai International Stadium March 4 - Semifinal 1 - Dubai International Stadium","2025-02-23T12:34:47.336011Z"
27,"1","2025-02-23T12:37:21.875747Z",25,"[{""start"":4,""end"":39,""text"":""International Cricket Council (ICC)"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":43,""end"":52,""text"":""Wednesday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":100,""end"":130,""text"":""ICC Mens Champions Trophy 2025"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":166,""end"":174,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":183,""end"":209,""text"":""United Arab Emirates (UAE)"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":215,""end"":237,""text"":""February 19 to March 9"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":258,""end"":262,""text"":""four"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":271,""end"":278,""text"":""Karachi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":280,""end"":286,""text"":""Lahore"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":292,""end"":302,""text"":""Rawalpindi"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":306,""end"":314,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":320,""end"":325,""text"":""Dubai"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":333,""end"":336,""text"":""UAE"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":349,""end"":351,""text"":""12"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":361,""end"":364,""text"":""six"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":394,""end"":414,""text"":""ICC Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":418,""end"":422,""text"":""2017"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":450,""end"":471,""text"":""Richard Kettleborough"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":575,""end"":589,""text"":""Chris Gaffaney"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":591,""end"":607,""text"":""Kumar Dharmasena"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":609,""end"":628,""text"":""Richard Illingworth"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":630,""end"":642,""text"":""Paul Reiffel"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":648,""end"":658,""text"":""Rod Tucker"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":660,""end"":673,""text"":""Michael Gough"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":675,""end"":691,""text"":""Adrian Holdstock"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":693,""end"":703,""text"":""Ahsan Raza"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":705,""end"":729,""text"":""Sharfuddoula Ibne Shahid"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":731,""end"":741,""text"":""Alex Wharf"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":747,""end"":758,""text"":""Joel Wilson"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":790,""end"":808,""text"":""2023 ODI World Cup"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":512,""end"":528,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":537,""end"":542,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":547,""end"":555,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":812,""end"":817,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":920,""end"":930,""text"":""David Boon"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":932,""end"":948,""text"":""Ranjan Madugalle"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":954,""end"":968,""text"":""Andrew Pycroft"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":970,""end"":974,""text"":""Boon"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":990,""end"":994,""text"":""2017"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":995,""end"":1017,""text"":""Champions Trophy final"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":1025,""end"":1034,""text"":""Madugalle"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1065,""end"":1069,""text"":""2013"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":1070,""end"":1075,""text"":""final"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":1081,""end"":1088,""text"":""Pycroft"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1110,""end"":1114,""text"":""2017"",""labels"":[""DATE""]}]",151.142,"The International Cricket Council (ICC) on Wednesday confirmed the match officials for the upcoming ICC Mens Champions Trophy 2025. The tournament, to be held across Pakistan and the United Arab Emirates (UAE) from February 19 to March 9, will take place in four venues: Karachi, Lahore, and Rawalpindi in Pakistan, and Dubai in the UAE. A panel of 12 umpires, six of whom also featured in the ICC Champions Trophy in 2017, will officiate the event. Richard Kettleborough, who stood in the final of the previous Champions Trophy between India and Pakistan, will be joined by Chris Gaffaney, Kumar Dharmasena, Richard Illingworth, Paul Reiffel, and Rod Tucker. Michael Gough, Adrian Holdstock, Ahsan Raza, Sharfuddoula Ibne Shahid, Alex Wharf, and Joel Wilson, all of whom officiated at the 2023 ODI World Cup in India, are the other umpires who will feature in the tournament. The panel of match referees will be led by David Boon, Ranjan Madugalle, and Andrew Pycroft. Boon officiated the 2017 Champions Trophy final, while Madugalle returns after officiating the 2013 final, and Pycroft also featured in the 2017 tournament.","2025-02-23T12:37:21.875776Z"
28,"1","2025-02-23T12:40:26.306631Z",26,"[{""start"":0,""end"":13,""text"":""Jacob Bethell"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":40,""end"":56,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":99,""end"":105,""text"":""second"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":136,""end"":141,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":106,""end"":127,""text"":""one-day international"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":183,""end"":190,""text"":""Bethell"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":171,""end"":173,""text"":""21"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":196,""end"":198,""text"":""51"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":221,""end"":230,""text"":""last week"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":251,""end"":257,""text"":""Sunday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":261,""end"":266,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":286,""end"":289,""text"":""2-0"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":302,""end"":307,""text"":""three"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":324,""end"":331,""text"":""Cuttack"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":337,""end"":361,""text"":""50-over Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":372,""end"":383,""text"":""February 19"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":387,""end"":395,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":400,""end"":405,""text"":""Dubai"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":423,""end"":430,""text"":""Bethell"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":458,""end"":474,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":498,""end"":509,""text"":""Jos Buttler"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":525,""end"":533,""text"":""Englands"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":534,""end"":538,""text"":""four"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":742,""end"":749,""text"":""England"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":789,""end"":797,""text"":""Bethells"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":825,""end"":833,""text"":""Somerset"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":842,""end"":852,""text"":""Tom Banton"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":856,""end"":862,""text"":""Sunday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":894,""end"":900,""text"":""Banton"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":902,""end"":904,""text"":""26"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":927,""end"":932,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":936,""end"":942,""text"":""Monday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":956,""end"":963,""text"":""England"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":1007,""end"":1016,""text"":""Ahmedabad"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":1020,""end"":1029,""text"":""Wednesday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":1031,""end"":1037,""text"":""Banton"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1052,""end"":1055,""text"":""six"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":1082,""end"":1084,""text"":""58"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":1098,""end"":1103,""text"":""26.80"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":1118,""end"":1126,""text"":""Englands"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":1205,""end"":1216,""text"":""February 22"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":1192,""end"":1201,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":1146,""end"":1162,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":1174,""end"":1183,""text"":""World Cup"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":1252,""end"":1263,""text"":""February 12"",""labels"":[""DATE""]}]",181.683,"Jacob Bethell is set to miss next weeks Champions Trophy after the left-handed batsman sat out the second one-day international against India with a hamstring injury. The 21-year-old Bethell made 51 in the opening defeat last week, but was missing on Sunday as India took an unbeatable 2-0 lead in the three-match series in Cuttack. The 50-over Champions Trophy begins on February 19 in Pakistan and Dubai. Im pretty sure (Bethell) has been ruled out of the Champions Trophy, to be honest, captain Jos Buttler admitted after Englands four-wicket defeat.  Thats really disappointing for him. Obviously, he played nicely the other day and has been one of the really exciting players, he added. Its a shame that injury is going to rule him out. England have not made an official statement on Bethells status, but they called up Somerset batsman Tom Banton on Sunday as cover. Wicketkeeper-batsman Banton, 26, was due to arrive in India on Monday and join the England squad for the final match of the series in Ahmedabad on Wednesday. Banton has played in six ODIs, with a top score of 58 and averages 26.80 with the bat. Englands first match in the Champions Trophy is against World Cup winners Australia on February 22. Final squads must be submitted by February 12.","2025-02-23T12:40:26.306655Z"
29,"1","2025-02-23T12:42:25.577199Z",27,"[{""start"":27,""end"":46,""text"":""Ravichandran Ashwin"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":7,""end"":12,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":106,""end"":118,""text"":""Shubman Gill"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":152,""end"":168,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":344,""end"":356,""text"":""Shubman Gill"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":490,""end"":496,""text"":""Ashwin"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":528,""end"":534,""text"":""Sunday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":618,""end"":630,""text"":""Test cricket"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":769,""end"":773,""text"":""Gill"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":815,""end"":825,""text"":""Axar Patel"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":882,""end"":886,""text"":""Pant"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":896,""end"":901,""text"":""Rahul"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1013,""end"":1025,""text"":""Shubman Gill"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1111,""end"":1122,""text"":""Virat Kohli"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1127,""end"":1141,""text"":""Jasprit Bumrah"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1143,""end"":1149,""text"":""Ashwin"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1180,""end"":1198,""text"":""2023 ODI World Cup"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":1213,""end"":1216,""text"":""ICC"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":1251,""end"":1262,""text"":""February 19"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":1266,""end"":1274,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":1279,""end"":1286,""text"":""the UAE"",""labels"":[""LOC""]}]",102.735,"Former India international Ravichandran Ashwin has backed the Indian team managements decision to appoint Shubman Gill as vice-captain for the upcoming Champions Trophy, describing it as a forward-thinking move. Think about who else in the current squad could be considered for the vice-captain role. Im not saying whether the decision to make Shubman Gill vice-captain was right or wrong, but the point raised is valid, especially since he was the vice-captain in the last series as well, Ashwin said on his YouTube channel on Sunday. I could be mistaken, but I believe hes also had some vice-captaincy experience in Test cricket. This could be a forward-thinking move, as the management might be considering who could take on the leadership role in the future. While Gill has been appointed the ODI vice-captain, Axar Patel has been handed the role in T20Is. While both (Rishabh) Pant and (KL) Rahul could play together, theyve handed the vice-captaincy to the player whose spot in the XI is already secure. If Shubman Gill is groomed to lead in the future, he can rely on the guidance of senior players like Virat Kohli and Jasprit Bumrah, Ashwin added. This squad mirrors the 2023 ODI World Cup, he said. The ICC event is scheduled to commence on February 19 in Pakistan and the UAE.","2025-02-23T12:42:25.577228Z"
30,"1","2025-02-23T12:45:02.964923Z",28,"[{""start"":18,""end"":29,""text"":""Pat Cummins"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":0,""end"":9,""text"":""Australia"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":58,""end"":74,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":92,""end"":107,""text"":""Andrew McDonald"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":111,""end"":120,""text"":""Wednesday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":122,""end"":129,""text"":""Cummins"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":213,""end"":218,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":226,""end"":249,""text"":""beginning of last month"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":286,""end"":297,""text"":""Test series"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":301,""end"":310,""text"":""Sri Lanka"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":335,""end"":341,""text"":""second"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":349,""end"":360,""text"":""Pat Cummins"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":432,""end"":440,""text"":""McDonald"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":471,""end"":474,""text"":""SEN"",""labels"":[""ORG""]},{""start"":479,""end"":486,""text"":""Cummins"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":496,""end"":504,""text"":""McDonald"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":515,""end"":526,""text"":""Travis Head"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":531,""end"":542,""text"":""Steve Smith"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":582,""end"":598,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":647,""end"":652,""text"":""Steve"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":609,""end"":614,""text"":""Smith"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":619,""end"":623,""text"":""Head"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":694,""end"":704,""text"":""Test match"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":714,""end"":723,""text"":""Sri Lanka"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":842,""end"":850,""text"":""McDonald"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":852,""end"":860,""text"":""McDonald"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":885,""end"":899,""text"":""Josh Hazlewood"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":924,""end"":938,""text"":""ODI tournament"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":940,""end"":949,""text"":""Hazlewood"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":975,""end"":986,""text"":""India tests"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":995,""end"":1009,""text"":""Sri Lanka tour"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":1039,""end"":1047,""text"":""McDonald"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1168,""end"":1182,""text"":""Mitchell Marsh"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1217,""end"":1233,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":1279,""end"":1286,""text"":""Feb. 19"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":1313,""end"":1321,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":1326,""end"":1350,""text"":""the United Arab Emirates"",""labels"":[""LOC""]}]",145.25,"Australia captain Pat Cummins is all but ruled out of the Champions Trophy, confirmed coach Andrew McDonald on Wednesday. Cummins has been troubled by an ankle injury that flared up after the test series win over India at the beginning of last month. The right-arm quick the missed the Test series in Sri Lanka due to the birth of his second child. Pat Cummins hasnt been able to resume any type of bowling so hes heavily unlikely, McDonald told Australian radio station SEN. In Cummins absence, McDonald projected Travis Head and Steve Smith as potential captaincy options for the Champions Trophy.  Theyre (Smith and Head) the two obvious ones. Steve has done a great job here in the (first) Test match (against Sri Lanka). Hes done some good work in one-day international cricket across the journey as well. So its between those two, said McDonald. McDonald also added that paceman Josh Hazlewood is also a doubt for the ODI tournament. Hazlewood missed three of the five India tests and the Sri Lanka tour with side and calf injuries. McDonald said he was battling to be fit and a decision would be made once medical information landed in coming days. All-rounder Mitchell Marsh has already been ruled out of the Champions Trophy with a back injury. The tournament starts on Feb. 19 and is being co-hosted by Pakistan and the United Arab Emirates..","2025-02-23T12:45:02.964940Z"
31,"1","2025-02-23T12:46:48.930527Z",29,"[{""start"":30,""end"":40,""text"":""Haris Rauf"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":80,""end"":86,""text"":""Monday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":0,""end"":9,""text"":""Pakistans"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":196,""end"":212,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":228,""end"":239,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":358,""end"":374,""text"":""National Stadium"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":330,""end"":335,""text"":""Haris"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":505,""end"":510,""text"":""Haris"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":531,""end"":540,""text"":""Pakistans"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":721,""end"":739,""text"":""three-nation event"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":819,""end"":829,""text"":""Akif Javed"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":871,""end"":882,""text"":""New Zealand"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":884,""end"":889,""text"":""Haris"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":904,""end"":906,""text"":""83"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":918,""end"":920,""text"":""46"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":921,""end"":943,""text"":""one-day internationals"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":956,""end"":959,""text"":""110"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":974,""end"":992,""text"":""T20 internationals"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":971,""end"":973,""text"":""79"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]},{""start"":1057,""end"":1062,""text"":""Haris"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1189,""end"":1202,""text"":""Khushdil Shah"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1204,""end"":1215,""text"":""Salman Agha"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1220,""end"":1233,""text"":""Kamran Ghulam"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1101,""end"":1104,""text"":""one"",""labels"":[""CARDINAL""]}]",103.904,"Pakistans injured fast bowler Haris Rauf said he resumed bowling in the nets on Monday and was feeling comfortable, adding that it was up to the team management to decide on his selection for the Champions Trophy opener against New Zealand. I have started doing exercises a few days back and also resumed bowling since yesterday, Haris told reporters at the National Stadium. I am feeling comfortable and my body is okay now the team management will decide about my playing in the opening match, he said. Haris, who remains one of Pakistans key fast bowlers with his express pace and ability to take wickets in the middle overs, sustained a muscular strain in his lower chest wall in the first match of the recently-held three-nation event.  But he has remained with the squad despite the selectors calling up uncapped Akif Javed as a backup after the first game against New Zealand. Haris has a haul of 83 wickets in 46 one-day internationals and another 110 wickets in 79 T20 internationals, having built his reputation as a specialist white-ball bowler. Haris also played down the presence of just one specialist spinner in the squad and noted that there were other spinners as well in Khushdil Shah, Salman Agha and Kamran Ghulam. I think we have always formed a good bowling combination with pace and spin and it will not be different in the tournament.","2025-02-23T12:46:48.930548Z"
32,"1","2025-02-23T12:48:50.969617Z",30,"[{""start"":20,""end"":45,""text"":""2025 ICC Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":61,""end"":69,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":78,""end"":89,""text"":""19 February"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":94,""end"":106,""text"":""9 March 2025"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":148,""end"":155,""text"":""Tuesday"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":157,""end"":167,""text"":""January 28"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":330,""end"":346,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":414,""end"":424,""text"":""3 February"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":439,""end"":458,""text"":""TCS Express centres"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":466,""end"":474,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":543,""end"":548,""text"":""India"",""labels"":[""GPE""]},{""start"":573,""end"":578,""text"":""Dubai"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":580,""end"":600,""text"":""United Arab Emirates"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":604,""end"":634,""text"":""20 and 23 February and 2 March"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":659,""end"":690,""text"":""ICC Mens Champions Trophy Final"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":716,""end"":730,""text"":""Sunday 9 March"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":887,""end"":917,""text"":""ICC Mens Champions Trophy 2025"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":963,""end"":971,""text"":""Pakistan"",""labels"":[""LOC""]},{""start"":1025,""end"":1029,""text"":""1996"",""labels"":[""DATE""]},{""start"":1061,""end"":1074,""text"":""Anurag Dahiya"",""labels"":[""PER""]},{""start"":1085,""end"":1101,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":1338,""end"":1354,""text"":""Champions Trophy"",""labels"":[""EVENT""]},{""start"":1361,""end"":1365,""text"":""2017"",""labels"":[""DATE""]}]",120.908,"The tickets for the 2025 ICC Champions Trophy, to be held in Pakistan between 19 February and 9 March 2025, will be available for general sale from Tuesday, January 28. Tickets for group stage matches and the second semi-final to be played will be available at 1:00 pm GST (2:30 pm IST/ 9:00 am GMT) and can be bought through the Champions Trophy website. Physical tickets will also be available for purchase from 3 February at designated TCS Express centres across Pakistan, with details to be announced in due course. Ticket information for India matches to be played in Dubai, United Arab Emirates on 20 and 23 February and 2 March is yet to be announced. ICC Mens Champions Trophy Final tickets  to be played on Sunday 9 March - will be available for purchase following the conclusion of the first semi-final in Dubai. We are thrilled to announce the official ticket on sale for the ICC Mens Champions Trophy 2025. This is a significant moment for cricket in Pakistan, hosting their first global cricket tournament since 1996, ICC Chief Commercial Officer, Anurag Dahiya said. The Champions Trophy promises to be an unmissable event where every match counts showcasing exciting cricket, featuring the worlds best teams competing for the coveted white jackets. We encourage fans to not miss out and get their tickets now for the first Champions Trophy since 2017, he added.","2025-02-23T12:48:50.969639Z"
